Pamela Silva

Dublin, County Dublin, Ireland



pamelanascimento3101@gmail.com



0833203696



linkedin.com/in/pamela-silva-419780156

Summary

Bilingual Customer service manager (Portuguese and English). I have been employed in customer service for over 5 years. Having started my career as a customer service specialist in 2013, I have since progressed to customer service management positions. my long term experience in the service industry has taught me how to meet and exceed each customers expectations. Positioning all companies that I have worked for better exposure and greater marketability. A task I have performed with success many times.

Currently employed as receptionist at Clancourt Management, I am responsible for the delivery of high-quality customer service.

Areas of expertise: Management, Personal assistance, Customer Service, Receptionist, Microsoft office.

Experience

Receptionist

Clancourt Management

Aug 2022 - Present (7 months)

Checking in arriving visitors, providing access using security and access control system;

Operating the main reception phone system and inbox, including responding to all queries in a timely manner;

Answering, screening, and forwarding incoming phone calls.



Language Development and Cultural immersion

Career Break

Jan 2018 - Jul 2022 (4 years 7 months)

Period of time dedicated to linguistic development and cultural immersion within in English speaking environment. During this time I worked as a Waitress and as a Cleaner.



🎎 Office Manager

Pello Menos Franchising

Aug 2016 - Jan 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Answered, selected and forwarded incoming calls:

Handled communication with contractors undertaking maintenance on site;

Ordered office supplies and maintained stock inventory;

Organized meetings when requested; and Managed inbound and outbound correspondence via mail, telephone and in-person office visitors;

Controlled access to systems and accounts;

Followed problems through to resolution and Provided effective and efficient administration support to management, the team and broader business functions, while working as part of an overall department administrative team;

Administrated clients invoicing as well as the payment of invoices;

Maintained relationships B2B and B2C. https://pellomenos.com.br/

SERVICE Specialist

Senac RJ

Jul 2013 - Aug 2016 (3 years 2 months)

Prospected for new customers and Conducted market research and analysis;

Drafted commercial proposals and Liaising with all departments in relation to the processing of customer orders and contract renewals;

Followed Negotiations until sale was agreed;

Administrated and managed customer accounts;

Recorded customer personal information accurately;

Managed the communication between the Sales, Customer Relationship Team department and other internal departments;

Handled complaints or concerns through to solution.

https://www.senac.br

Education

Universidade Unigranrio | Afya

Bachelor's degree, Business

2008 - 2010

https://www.unigranrio.com.br/

NED training

English course 2018 - 2020 Level C1

Loide Martha

High School Diploma Jan 2005 - Dec 2008 https://loidemartha.com.br/

Skills

Data Entry • Communication • Teamwork • English • Microsoft Word • Customer Retention • Public Speaking • Web Content Writing • Account Management • Receptionist Duties